Hey everyone! It's time for another mini skirt video because it's been three years since the last one.
Can you believe it? That's how long I'm doing this already and even longer. Wow, crazy.
Anyway, I've got a lot of mini skirts today. Different materials and different shapes.
So I'm going to create four looks and I'll take you along.
I think they're quite cool all of them are rather coffee and dark but that's what I like so let's go
first outfit is this full PVC look because you have a PVC skirt corset top and even the boots
and the harness so it's black and shiny this skirt is from restyle and the top is from face
I've got them ages already as well as the boots I don't even know what brand the boots are
anyway I kind of love this look it's a lot I went all in here and it's probably not the most
comfortable look due to the corset here still I think it looks great with all the metal accessories
here the metal parts in the harness they pull the look together and every time when I think about
mini skirts. I'm not sure about the length. I think this is classified as a mini skirt
because it's pretty short actually. But I'm also wearing it in my waist and not on my hips. Then
it would be longer of course. But I like this look. It's cute but also bossy but also cute with the
here. So for the next outfit I have a green skirt, not black but the other ones are going to be black
afterwards. So let's switch to the only color I have here. It's giving schoolgirl my heat. I don't
know when I saw this skirt which was on sale so I bought it. I thought immediately it looks like a
school uniform kind of skirt so that's why I combined it with a blouse I also
bought on sale and I put some high socks on top of the tights to give even more
school wear vibes I don't know especially with the hair kind of cute
don't you think? This is the only colorful skirt I have in this video.
Colorful because the other ones are all black and I know in my first video I showed
like red and rainbow and whatever but I simply didn't buy a lot of skirts in the
last three years. This one being the exception. So I don't have any red and
rainbow colored skirts anymore and most of it is black which is fine by me actually.
The four-leather skirt here and the four-leather top is a lot together especially with all the
accessories but I think that's quite cool. Also I chose the heels that go well with the metal
parts because they have metal spikes yay and here's a metal spike too and yeah the belt is
brand new first time i'm wearing it i think it's really really cool it's from disturbia
this skirt is really old and the top as well i think this was peter domini
but yeah heels are giaro and tights are just some random no-name tights because i just try
them all the time so it's easier to use cheap ones yeah it's like giving a lot
of sounds but I think it's quite cool I would wear this for going out to my
favorite golf club or on a nice and not too warm festival day because the top is
quite warm so it's great for I don't know slightly rain 20 degree festival day it's still really cool
I would not wear these shoes for festival day because as nice as they look they are not for
walking or standing around too long mainly for photo shoots and videos I hope you like this look
I think it's really cool off to the next one
the last look and I can tell you this skirt is so old I think I bought it when I was
19 something like that so almost 15 years ago and I still own it because it was very very dear to
me when I was younger and started to go out in the goth scene and wanted to have a cool outfit
So I've worn a lot more mini skirts in the past. I don't know why I switched to
leggings. Maybe because it's easier because you don't have to combine it. But
I combined this skirt here with the boots. They fit to the harness. I put them
top to top. Top to top, yeah. And also fishnets because you can never go wrong
with a fishnet look here and I think it fits pretty good together it's giving a
bit of Brett and Avril Lavigne vibes skirt I think anyway the harness is also
pretty cool it's from Sapius a small label from Berlin I link in the
description text whatever I can link whatever is available still because
obviously the skirt isn't anymore and yeah this was my final look I hope you
enjoyed this video and you had fun exploring different mini skirt looks
with me I think that's it for today hit the subscribe button and check out my
patreon because there's a lot of behind-the-scenes material on my patreon
my youtube channel got demonetized a few years ago so if you want to support me
and these videos check out patreon also write a comment and tell me which one
was your favorite look and I will see you in the next video have a nice day
bye